Name: Igor Tosic

Date of Birth: 24.07.1980

Email: igortosic1980@gmail.com

Mob: +4745832552



### **Profile:**

I have 18 years working experience in different types of industry, such as Broadcast Media, IT/Computer and software, government and private sector and Digital Marketing. I am available to work in a variety of environments with modern technologies.

As the web developer, my focus is on developing web applications, UX, working with APIs, data analyst, converting, marketing automation, authentication and authorization.

#### **Tech Stacks:**

- · HTML5, CSS, SCSS
- · JavaScript, TypeScript
- · React, Express, NodeJS
- · GraphQL, Apollo GraphQL, MongoDB
- · Semantic UI, Bootstrap, Material Design
- · Django CMS, EVOQ, WordPress
- · Cloud: Heroku, DIVIO, GCloud
- · Digital design, video production, advertising

### **Experience:**

#### 06.2019 - present

## Frontend Developer UX/UI at Sentinel Software AS, Norway (<a href="https://carweb.no/">https://carweb.no/</a>)

- · Working on developing existing and new features
- · Contribute and develop UX/UI
- · Analyse UX, working with mockups
- · working on product documentations (UI library, components, props)

#### 09.2016 - 05.2019

#### Web developer at Sticos AS, Norway (<u>www.sticos.no</u>)

- · Web developing
- · Working with Big Data, APIs and web personalization
- · Marketing automation with Marketo
- · DNN/EVOQ CMS
- · Video production

#### 07.2015 - 05.2016

#### Web developer at Plapre AS, Norway (www.plapre.com)

- · Working on ICT and technical developing solutions
- · Front-end and UX development
- · Backend PHP developing
- · Contribute to products development and improvement of existing products

#### 04.2014 - 06.2015

# Web developer and Multimedia designer - part-time at Cyber Team, Serbia

(www.cyberteam.rs)

- · HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript
- · digital design, video production, advertising, Google Ad Words,
- · Word Press, SEO/SEM, Affiliate and Viral marketing, Website optimization
- · IT strategy, e-commerce
- · Visual communication
- PHP and MySQL
- · Bootstrap, Foundation

#### 10.2009 - 04.2014

# Expert associate The Coordination Body the Government of the Republic Serbia for the Municipalities of Presevo, Bujanovac and Medvedja - http://www.kt.gov.rs/

- · Video editing, post-production and shooting
- · Graphics design, advertising
- · On line promotion, workshop teaching

09.2005 - 06.2011

Founder and CTO of Agency Easymindstudio, Serbia- a partnership with Cyberteam, Serbia igortosic.com, vimeo.com/igortosic,

flickr.com/photos/igortosic/, www.youtube.com/user/igortosicvideo

- · Video editing, post-production and shooting
- · Graphics design, advertising
- · SEO/SEM
- · HTML. CSS

#### 06.2004 - 09.2007

# Database administrator and post-production editor in TV Studio Valjevo (www.tvvaplus.rs)

- · developing a database and implementing
- · implementing the basic forms of data protection
- · Video editing, post-production
- · Graphics design, advertising
- · manage documents and keep them in different versions

#### 11.2002 - 06.2004

#### Video editor and graphics designer in Radio Television Serbia for regional program

- · Graphics design, advertising
- · Video editing, post production

11.2002 - 09.2012

TV B92, Belgrade, Serbia, videographer (part time) <a href="http://www.b92.net/">http://www.b92.net/</a>

10.2000 - 10.2002

IT operator and videographer in TV Vujic, Serbiahttp://www.vtv.rs/

· Live TV programs, studio programs, editing video, network and live room operation

#### **Education:**

2017 /2018 Udacity, Nanodegree - Full Stack Web Developer

10.2003 - 07.2009 High Business School of vocational studies (BA in Business IT), Valjevo, Serbia

11.2011 - 11.2012 IT Academy, Belgrade - Java Development (one-year course)